[
    { "question" : "být", "answer" : "to be", "pronunciation" : "/bi:t/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "mít", "answer" : "to have", "pronunciation" : "/mi:t/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "dělat", "answer" : "to do", "pronunciation" : "/ɟɛlat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "říkat", "answer" : "to say", "pronunciation" : "/r̝i:kat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vidět", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "/vɪdjɛt/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "jít", "answer" : "to go", "pronunciation" : "/ji:t/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "chtít", "answer" : "to want", "pronunciation" : "/xti:t/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vědět", "answer" : "to know", "pronunciation" : "/vɛdjɛt/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "dát", "answer" : "to give", "pronunciation" : "/da:t/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "pracovat", "answer" : "to work", "pronunciation" : "/pratsovat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "hledat", "answer" : "to look for", "pronunciation" : "/hlɛdat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "jet", "answer" : "to travel", "pronunciation" : "/jɛt/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "stát se", "answer" : "to become", "pronunciation" : "/sta:t sɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "myslet", "answer" : "to think", "pronunciation" : "/mɪslɛt/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "mluvit", "answer" : "to speak", "pronunciation" : "/mlu:vɪt/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "potřebovat", "answer" : "to need", "pronunciation" : "/potr̝ɛbovat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "cestovat", "answer" : "to travel", "pronunciation" : "/t͡sɛstovat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "psát", "answer" : "to write", "pronunciation" : "/psa:t/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "čekat", "answer" : "to wait", "pronunciation" : "/t͡ʃɛkat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "znamenat", "answer" : "to mean", "pronunciation" : "/znamɛnat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "získat", "answer" : "to obtain", "pronunciation" : "/zi:skat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "vidět", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "/vɪdjɛt/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "zůstat", "answer" : "to stay", "pronunciation" : "/zu:stat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "pracovat", "answer" : "to work", "pronunciation" : "/pratsovat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "dělat", "answer" : "to do", "pronunciation" : "/ɟɛlat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "chodit", "answer" : "to walk", "pronunciation" : "/xodɪt/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "dýchat", "answer" : "to breathe", "pronunciation" : "/di:xa:t/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "číst", "answer" : "to read", "pronunciation" : "/t͡ʃi:st/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "moci", "answer" : "to be able to", "pronunciation" : "/mot͡si/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "jíst", "answer" : "to eat", "pronunciation" : "/ji:st/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "milovat", "answer" : "to love", "pronunciation" : "/mɪlovat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "hovořit", "answer" : "to talk", "pronunciation" : "/hovor̝i:t/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "zavolat", "answer" : "to call", "pronunciation" : "/zavolat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "platit", "answer" : "to pay", "pronunciation" : "/platɪt/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "hledat", "answer" : "to look for", "pronunciation" : "/hlɛdat/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "pomoci", "answer" : "to help", "pronunciation" : "/pomot͡si/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "spát", "answer" : "to sleep", "pronunciation" : "/spa:t/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "změnit se", "answer" : "to change", "pronunciation" : "/zmɲɛnɪt sɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "sedět", "answer" : "to sit", "pronunciation" : "/sɛdjɛt/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "snažit se", "answer" : "to try", "pronunciation" : "/sna:ʒɪt sɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "rozhodnout se", "answer" : "to decide", "pronunciation" : "/rozɦodnout sɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "stát", "answer" : "to cost", "pronunciation" : "/sta:t/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "dům", "answer" : "house", "pronunciation" : "/duːm/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "stůl", "answer" : "table", "pronunciation" : "/stuːl/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "kůň", "answer" : "horse", "pronunciation" : "/kuːɲ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "kniha", "answer" : "book", "pronunciation" : "/kɲiha/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "člověk", "answer" : "person", "pronunciation" : "/tʃlovjɛk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "voda", "answer" : "water", "pronunciation" : "/voda/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "strom", "answer" : "tree", "pronunciation" : "/strom/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "okno", "answer" : "window", "pronunciation" : "/okno/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "dítě", "answer" : "child", "pronunciation" : "/diːtjɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "hory", "answer" : "mountains", "pronunciation" : "/horɪ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ryba", "answer" : "fish", "pronunciation" : "/rɪba/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "nůž", "answer" : "knife", "pronunciation" : "/nuːʃ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "pták", "answer" : "bird", "pronunciation" : "/ptak/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "kolo", "answer" : "wheel", "pronunciation" : "/kolo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "čas", "answer" : "time", "pronunciation" : "/tʃas/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "auto", "answer" : "car", "pronunciation" : "/auto/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "pes", "answer" : "dog", "pronunciation" : "/pɛs/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "hrad", "answer" : "castle", "pronunciation" : "/hrad/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "jablko", "answer" : "apple", "pronunciation" : "/jablko/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "řeka", "answer" : "river", "pronunciation" : "/r̝ɛka/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "kočka", "answer" : "cat", "pronunciation" : "/kotʃka/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "žena", "answer" : "woman", "pronunciation" : "/ʒɛna/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "muž", "answer" : "man", "pronunciation" : "/mʊʃ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "dveře", "answer" : "door", "pronunciation" : "/dvɛrjɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "hora", "answer" : "mountain", "pronunciation" : "/hora/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "město", "answer" : "city", "pronunciation" : "/mɛsto/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "louka", "answer" : "meadow", "pronunciation" : "/louka/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "káva", "answer" : "coffee", "pronunciation" : "/kaːva/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "rádio", "answer" : "radio", "pronunciation" : "/raːdjo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "koření", "answer" : "spice", "pronunciation" : "/kor̝ɛɲiː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "krev", "answer" : "blood", "pronunciation" : "/krɛv/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "čaj", "answer" : "tea", "pronunciation" : "/tʃaj/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "obloha", "answer" : "sky", "pronunciation" : "/obloha/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "slunce", "answer" : "sun", "pronunciation" : "/slunt͡sɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "láska", "answer" : "love", "pronunciation" : "/laːska/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "dešť", "answer" : "rain", "pronunciation" : "/dɛʃtj/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "lidi", "answer" : "people", "pronunciation" : "/lɪdɪ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "týden", "answer" : "week", "pronunciation" : "/tiːdɛn/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "oheň", "answer" : "fire", "pronunciation" : "/ohɛɲ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "křeslo", "answer" : "chair", "pronunciation" : "/kr̝ɛslo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "měsíc", "answer" : "moon", "pronunciation" : "/mɛsiːt͡s/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "barva", "answer" : "color", "pronunciation" : "/barva/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "kost", "answer" : "bone", "pronunciation" : "/kost/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ovoce", "answer" : "fruit", "pronunciation" : "/ovoʦɛ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "písek", "answer" : "sand", "pronunciation" : "/piːsɛk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "sklo", "answer" : "glass", "pronunciation" : "/sklo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "kapela", "answer" : "band", "pronunciation" : "/kapɛla/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "tráva", "answer" : "grass", "pronunciation" : "/traːva/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "věc", "answer" : "thing", "pronunciation" : "/vɛt͡s/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "dobrý", "answer" : "good", "pronunciation" : "/dobree/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "špatný", "answer" : "bad", "pronunciation" : "/shpahtnee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "velký", "answer" : "big", "pronunciation" : "/velkee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "malý", "answer" : "small", "pronunciation" : "/malee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "nový", "answer" : "new", "pronunciation" : "/no-vee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "starý", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "/starree/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "krásný", "answer" : "beautiful", "pronunciation" : "/krahsnee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "hnusný", "answer" : "ugly", "pronunciation" : "/hnoosnee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "levný", "answer" : "cheap", "pronunciation" : "/levenee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "drahý", "answer" : "expensive", "pronunciation" : "/drahhee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "rychlý", "answer" : "fast", "pronunciation" : "/rickhlee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "pomalý", "answer" : "slow", "pronunciation" : "/pomallee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "silný", "answer" : "strong", "pronunciation" : "/seelnee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "slabý", "answer" : "weak", "pronunciation" : "/slabee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "těžký", "answer" : "heavy", "pronunciation" : "/tezhkee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "lehký", "answer" : "light", "pronunciation" : "/lehkee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "vysoký", "answer" : "high", "pronunciation" : "/veesokee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "nízký", "answer" : "low", "pronunciation" : "/neezkee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "široký", "answer" : "wide", "pronunciation" : "/sheerokee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "úzký", "answer" : "narrow", "pronunciation" : "/ooskee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "teplý", "answer" : "warm", "pronunciation" : "/tehplee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "studený", "answer" : "cold", "pronunciation" : "/stoo-den-ee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "plný", "answer" : "full", "pronunciation" : "/plnee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "prázdný", "answer" : "empty", "pronunciation" : "/prahzdnee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "hlučný", "answer" : "noisy", "pronunciation" : "/hloochn-ee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "tichý", "answer" : "quiet", "pronunciation" : "/teekhee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "jednoduchý", "answer" : "simple", "pronunciation" : "/yed-noh-doo-khee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "složitý", "answer" : "complicated", "pronunciation" : "/slo-zhee-tee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "hezký", "answer" : "pretty", "pronunciation" : "/heh-skee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "pěkný", "answer" : "nice", "pronunciation" : "/pehknee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "zlý", "answer" : "mean", "pronunciation" : "/zlee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "dobrá", "answer" : "good", "pronunciation" : "/dobrah/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "špatná", "answer" : "bad", "pronunciation" : "/shpaht-nah/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "velká", "answer" : "big", "pronunciation" : "/velka/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "malá", "answer" : "small", "pronunciation" : "/mala/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "nová", "answer" : "new", "pronunciation" : "/no-vah/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "stará", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "/starah/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "krásná", "answer" : "beautiful", "pronunciation" : "/krahsna/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "hnusná", "answer" : "ugly", "pronunciation" : "/hnoosnah/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "levná", "answer" : "cheap", "pronunciation" : "/levna/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "drahá", "answer" : "expensive", "pronunciation" : "/drahah/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "rychlá", "answer" : "fast", "pronunciation" : "/rickhlah/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "pomalá", "answer" : "slow", "pronunciation" : "/pomalah/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "silná", "answer" : "strong", "pronunciation" : "/seelnah/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "slabá", "answer" : "weak", "pronunciation" : "/slabah/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "těžká", "answer" : "heavy", "pronunciation" : "/tezhka/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ano", "answer" : "yes", "pronunciation" : "/ah-no/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ne", "answer" : "no", "pronunciation" : "/neh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "tady", "answer" : "here", "pronunciation" : "/tah-dee/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "tam", "answer" : "there", "pronunciation" : "/tahm/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "dnes", "answer" : "today", "pronunciation" : "/dnes/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "včera", "answer" : "yesterday", "pronunciation" : "/vuh-cheh-rah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "zítra", "answer" : "tomorrow", "pronunciation" : "/zee-trah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "teď", "answer" : "now", "pronunciation" : "/tehd/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "pak", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/pahk/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "možná", "answer" : "maybe", "pronunciation" : "/mohzh-nah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "často", "answer" : "often", "pronunciation" : "/chah-stoh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "málo", "answer" : "little", "pronunciation" : "/mah-loh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "hodně", "answer" : "a lot", "pronunciation" : "/hohd-nyeh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "rád", "answer" : "gladly", "pronunciation" : "/rahd/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ráda", "answer" : "gladly", "pronunciation" : "/rah-dah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "také", "answer" : "also", "pronunciation" : "/tah-keh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "nikdy", "answer" : "never", "pronunciation" : "/neek-dy/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "už", "answer" : "already", "pronunciation" : "/oosh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ještě", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "/yesh-tyeh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "tamhle", "answer" : "over there", "pronunciation" : "/tahm-leh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "sem", "answer" : "here", "pronunciation" : "/sehm/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "tamtudy", "answer" : "that way", "pronunciation" : "/tahm-too-dy/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "zde", "answer" : "here", "pronunciation" : "/zdeh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "zdejší", "answer" : "local", "pronunciation" : "/zdeh-yee/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "dneska", "answer" : "today", "pronunciation" : "/dnes-kah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "včerašek", "answer" : "yesterday", "pronunciation" : "/vuh-cheh-rah-shek/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "zítraješí", "answer" : "tomorrow", "pronunciation" : "/zee-trah-yeh-shee/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "opravdu", "answer" : "really", "pronunciation" : "/oh-prahv-doo/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "jistě", "answer" : "certainly", "pronunciation" : "/yee-styeh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "snadno", "answer" : "easily", "pronunciation" : "/snahd-noh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "špatně", "answer" : "badly", "pronunciation" : "/shpaht-nyeh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "pomalu", "answer" : "slowly", "pronunciation" : "/poh-mah-loo/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "rychle", "answer" : "quickly", "pronunciation" : "/reeh-khleh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "pečlivě", "answer" : "carefully", "pronunciation" : "/peh-chlee-veh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "sice", "answer" : "indeed", "pronunciation" : "/see-tseh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "vůbec", "answer" : "at all", "pronunciation" : "/voo-behts/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "všechno", "answer" : "everything", "pronunciation" : "/vshen-choh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "nic", "answer" : "nothing", "pronunciation" : "/neets/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "někdy", "answer" : "sometimes", "pronunciation" : "/nyehk-dy/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "úplně", "answer" : "completely", "pronunciation" : "/oopl-nyeh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "tedy", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/teh-dy/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "přece", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "/preh-tseh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "navíc", "answer" : "moreover", "pronunciation" : "/nah-veets/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "prostě", "answer" : "simply", "pronunciation" : "/proh-styeh/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "a", "answer" : "and", "pronunciation" : "/ah/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ale", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "/ah-leh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "avšak", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "/ahv-shahk/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "jak", "answer" : "as", "pronunciation" : "/yahk/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "když", "answer" : "when", "pronunciation" : "/kdeesh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "nebo", "answer" : "or", "pronunciation" : "/neh-boh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "protože", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/proh-toh-zheh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "že", "answer" : "that", "pronunciation" : "/zheh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "jako", "answer" : "like", "pronunciation" : "/yah-koh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ani", "answer" : "neither", "pronunciation" : "/ah-nee/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "aniž", "answer" : "without", "pronunciation" : "/ah-neezh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "dokud", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/doh-koot/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "kromě", "answer" : "except", "pronunciation" : "/kroh-meh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "než", "answer" : "than", "pronunciation" : "/nehsh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ovšem", "answer" : "of course", "pronunciation" : "/ohv-shem/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "pak", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/pahk/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "proto", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/proh-toh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "sice", "answer" : "indeed", "pronunciation" : "/see-tseh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "tak", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "/tahk/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "totiž", "answer" : "namely", "pronunciation" : "/toh-teesh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "však", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "/v-shahk/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "přestože", "answer" : "although", "pronunciation" : "/prehs-toh-zheh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "poté", "answer" : "after that", "pronunciation" : "/poh-teh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "tudíž", "answer" : "thus", "pronunciation" : "/too-deezh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "buď", "answer" : "either", "pronunciation" : "/bood/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "což", "answer" : "which", "pronunciation" : "/tsohzh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "čímž", "answer" : "which", "pronunciation" : "/cheemzh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "jakmile", "answer" : "as soon as", "pronunciation" : "/yahk-mee-leh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "jestliže", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "/yest-lee-zheh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "kromě toho", "answer" : "besides that", "pronunciation" : "/kroh-meh tohoh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "mezitím", "answer" : "meanwhile", "pronunciation" : "/meh-zee-teem/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "naproti", "answer" : "opposite", "pronunciation" : "/nah-proh-tee/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "podobně", "answer" : "similarly", "pronunciation" : "/poh-dohb-neh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "pořád", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "/poh-ryahd/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "potom", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/poh-tohm/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "přesto", "answer" : "nevertheless", "pronunciation" : "/prehs-toh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "skrze", "answer" : "through", "pronunciation" : "/skr-zheh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "snad", "answer" : "perhaps", "pronunciation" : "/snahd/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "spíše", "answer" : "rather", "pronunciation" : "/spee-sheh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "stejně", "answer" : "equally", "pronunciation" : "/stay-nyeh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "už", "answer" : "already", "pronunciation" : "/oosh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "všude", "answer" : "everywhere", "pronunciation" : "/v-shoo-deh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ať", "answer" : "whether", "pronunciation" : "/aht/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "cožpak", "answer" : "how come", "pronunciation" : "/tsohzh-pahk/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "dokonce", "answer" : "even", "pronunciation" : "/doh-kohn-tseh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "hlavně", "answer" : "mainly", "pronunciation" : "/hlav-nyeh/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]